module.exports = [
  {
    question:
      'In the "Harry Potter" series, what is the name of the prison where dangerous wizards are held?',
    correctAnswer: "Azkaban",
    wrongAnswers: ["Alcatraz", "Devil's Island", "Sing Sing"],
  },
  {
    question:
      'Who played the role of Legolas in "The Lord of the Rings" trilogy?',
    correctAnswer: "Orlando Bloom",
    wrongAnswers: ["Viggo Mortensen", "Elijah Wood", "Sean Astin"],
  },
  {
    question:
      'What is the name of the hobbit played by Elijah Wood in "The Lord of the Rings" trilogy?',
    correctAnswer: "Frodo Baggins",
    wrongAnswers: ["Bilbo Baggins", "Samwise Gamgee", "Peregrin Took"],
  },
  {
    question:
      'In the movie "The Chronicles of Narnia: The Lion, the Witch and the Wardrobe", what is the name of the evil queen who rules over Narnia?',
    correctAnswer: "Jadis",
    wrongAnswers: ["Maleficent", "Ursula", "Cruella de Vil"],
  },
  {
    question:
      'What is the name of the dragon in the animated movie "How to Train Your Dragon"?',
    correctAnswer: "Toothless",
    wrongAnswers: ["Smaug", "Falkor", "Mushu"],
  },
  {
    question:
      'In the movie "The NeverEnding Story" (1984), what is the name of the young hero who sets out to save the magical land of Fantasia?',
    correctAnswer: "Atreyu",
    wrongAnswers: ["Bastian", "Falcor", "Gmork"],
  },
  {
    question: 'Who directed the movie "Pan\'s Labyrinth" (2006)?',
    correctAnswer: "Guillermo del Toro",
    wrongAnswers: ["Tim Burton", "Peter Jackson", "James Cameron"],
  },
  {
    question:
      'In the movie "The Princess Bride" (1987), what is the name of the hero who must rescue his true love from a group of villains?',
    correctAnswer: "Westley",
    wrongAnswers: ["Prince Humperdinck", "Inigo Montoya", "Fezzik"],
  },
  {
    question: 'Who played the role of Hagrid in the "Harry Potter" movies?',
    correctAnswer: "Robbie Coltrane",
    wrongAnswers: ["Alan Rickman", "Gary Oldman", "Kenneth Branagh"],
  },
  {
    question:
      "Who played the character of Harry Potter in the Harry Potter series?",
    correctAnswer: "Daniel Radcliffe",
    wrongAnswers: ["Tom Felton", "Matthew Lewis", "Rupert Grint"],
  },
  {
    question:
      'In the movie "Labyrinth" (1986), what is the name of the Goblin King who kidnaps the protagonist\'s baby brother?',
    correctAnswer: "Jareth",
    wrongAnswers: ["Jared", "Jeremy", "Jax"],
  },
  {
    question:
      'Who played the role of Aslan in the "Chronicles of Narnia" movies?',
    correctAnswer: "Liam Neeson",
    wrongAnswers: ["Ian McKellen", "Anthony Hopkins", "James Earl Jones"],
  },
];
